These people are putting me down like this because
esta gente me están poniendo así porque
I have said something bad about Antonio David
yo he opinado algo malo de antonio david
that I have experienced myself and I have
que yo mismo he vivido haber y le he
put Maria Patiño's batteries okay and I have
puesto las pilas a maría patiño vale y
put her batteries amaría patrick you are
le he puesto de las pilas amaría patrick
not going to use the weapon on me I am
a mí no me vais a utilizar el arma yo
still against the television factory
sigo en contra de la fábrica de la tele
and all the videos that I have made
y todos los vídeos que yo he hecho en
against the television factory I have
contra de la fábrica de la tele
made myself he has not asked me
los he hecho yo a mí no me ha mandado
anything to do it myself what I have said is
nada de hacerlo yo lo que he dicho ha
that Antonio David it is not true that he has
sido que antonio david no es verdad que
never asked us for anything yes it
no nos ha pedido nunca nada que sí que
is true that on some occasions he has
es verdad que en alguna ocasión nos ha
told us hey sometimes the video in fact listen
dicho oye a veces el vídeo de hecho oye
to see if you pay attention to this hashtag
a ver si así le dais bola este hashtag
yes but we have paid attention to him
eso sí pero nosotros le hemos hecho caso
we have not paid attention to him but
nosotros no le hemos hecho caso pero
all the videos that I have made
todos los vídeos que yo he hecho durante
throughout the year which is my work and my
todo el año que es mi trabajo y mis
videos are from before I spoke to
vídeos son anteriores a yo hablarme con
Antonio David all those videos are mine,
antonio david todos esos vídeos son míos
my own creation and my research and
de mi cosecha y de mi investigaciones y
my work
de mi trabajo